const card_categories = {
  "j-angielski-food": {
    name: "j. angielski - food",
    cards: [
      { front: "truskawka", back: "strawberry" },
      { front: "gałka muszkatołowa", back: "nutmeg" },
      { front: "jabłko", back: "apple" },
      { front: "karczoch", back: "artichoke" },
      { front: "cielęcina", back: "veal" },
    ],
  },
  "stolice-europejskie": {
    name: "stolice europejskie",
    cards: [
      { front: "Holandia", back: "Amsterdam" },
      { front: "Włochy", back: "Rzym" },
      { front: "Niemcy", back: "Berlin" },
      { front: "Węgry", back: "Budapeszt" },
      { front: "Rumunia", back: "Bukareszt" },
    ],
  },
};

export function getCategorySummaries() {
  return Object.entries(card_categories).map(([id, category]) => {
    return { id, name: category.name };
  });
}

export function hasCategory(categoryId) {
  return card_categories.hasOwnProperty(categoryId);
}

export function getCategory(categoryId) {
  if (hasCategory(categoryId))
    return { id: categoryId, ...card_categories[categoryId] };
  return null;
}

export default {
  getCategorySummaries,
  hasCategory,
  getCategory,
};